ultrapro.com 2004-10-15

# ULTRA PRO - Storage solutions for collectibles, photos and multimedia

**Here at Ultra PRO, we value our customers!  
**With over 50 years of experience, here at UltraPRO, we know our most valued asset is the customer. Below you will find a brief description of our policies regarding your privacy, order shipping, and refunds. If you have any questions regarding any of these, please don't hesitate to contact us!

**Privacy Policy  
**This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for our website, UltraPRO.com 

UltraPRO LP has created this privacy policy to inform you of the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, www.ultrapro.com. We would hereby like to notify you of: 

**Information Collection and Use**   
Ultrapro.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Ultrapro.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

**Membership**  
When you make a purchase on our site, you provide the following information to UltraPro.com: 

Your name   
Your e-mail address   
Your billing and shipping address   
Your telephone number   
The type of credit card you are using if applicable   
Your credit card number and expiration date, or other form of payment 

**Order**  
We request information from the user on our order form when making a purchase. Here, is where a user must provide their contact information, like name and shipping address, and shipping information, like credit card number and expiration date. This information is used for billing purposes and to fill the customer's order. If we have difficulty processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Usage of a cookie from our site is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site. 

**Aggregate Information**  
UltraPro.com uses aggregate information from demographic surveys, traffic patterns and IP addresses to customize our site. Aggregate information is occasionally shared with partners of UltraPro.com to plan advertising or promotions. We do not share any personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**  
UltraPro.com does not share your information with any third party partners to provide you with certain services that are detailed below. We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

**Catalog, Newsletters, Etc.**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our catalog, newsletter, etc., we ask for contact information such as name, street address and email address to provide these communications. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the choice and opt-out section below. 

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send you an email; however, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Security  
**UltraPro.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via our website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - Secure Socket Layers (SSLs). While on a secure page, such as our order form, a lock icon appears on the bottom of your Web browser. When you are not on a secure page, no lock icon will appear. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information (like your credit card information) online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are fully informed about our security and privacy practices and updated as new policies are added or revised. They are regularly notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure that our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment under restricted access. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website you may contact us.

If we decided to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and otherplaces we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

top
